(in English) Hello!
(in English) No, please.
(in English) Good morning!
Welcome!
A small bus ride to the boat.
- Are you peppered?
- Yes a little!
We're going to jump on a boat.
Now we are far out on a pier.
Now you can go carefully.
Good!
- We will go this boat.
- Oh, what a nice!
Dad, check out everyone ...
(in English) Yes.
Thanks!
We had a really strange night.
Alma couldn't sleep, and we three were up to half past four.
Yes.
Nine we were picked up with the bus.
We were up at seven.
But it will be very exciting anyway!
- Fun to see the Thai island world.
- Yes, we should not just ride this big boat!
We are going to paddle kayak.
Into caves.
(in English) Do you want something to drink, sir?
(in English) Yes, please.
(in English) Coca-Cola or Sprite?
(in English) Sprite, please.
(in English) and you, a little drink?
(in English) Thanks, that's good.
(in English) No thanks, that's good.
- We arrive at our first stop.
- Yes!
- An island called ... - Panak Island.
- We will take a kayak into a beach and swim a little.
- Yes.
It will be great, because as soon as we stop moving forward with the boat ...
... as soon as it stops fan, it gets very hot!
Yes.
The island is crap!
- Hörrudu, you say so?
- Yes but ... shit means poop, and poop is not a swear word!
I think it's a swear word.
What do you think?
You can vote!
Should Alma get a fine?